[intriguing music playing]
[vocalizing]
[reporter] A mutant virus has emerged
in which patients begin
to exhibit symptoms within five minutes
in low-pressured environments.
A much faster pace compared
to previous incubation period of 24 hours.
Raising even greater concerns
in regards to containment.
After the outbreak,
the increase of symptoms
like abnormal physical ability
and violent tendencies
has led the infected
to display animal-like behaviors,
making it difficult
to secure quarantine facilities.
In the United States, more than
150,000 people have been infected,
mostly by US forces
returning home from serving in Korea,
and more than 30,000 have died.
North Korea is on the verge of collapse
with over eight and a half million
reported infected people,
representing a third
of the country's total population.
By contrast,
South Korea has just been declared
a DMZ Virus-free zone
by the World Health Organization today
when the last known infected person
known only as "Choi"
died after a thirteen-day illness.
To date, South Korea
has reported 345 total cases with 34--
[suspenseful music playing]
[man] Go.
[thrilling music playing]
MOTEL
[agent 1] Team Two, supporting the site.
Team Three, blocking the exit.
[bird cawing]
[thrilling music continues]
[brakes squealing]
[newscaster on TV]
The cause of the DMZ Virus
which was allegedly
first detected in the DMZ,
a symbol of the ceasefire between
North and South Korea, ten months ago,
has not yet been identified.
It has been 19 days since Dr. Jung
and his daughter have disappeared
while on their way to North Korea,
and there is no information
about their whereabouts.
Dr. Jung became quite famous,
after curing his daughter Ha-na
of the DMZ virus,
drawing the attention
of academics worldwide.
Dr. Jung had been en route
to the Sinuiju Chemical Weapons Institute
in order to mass produce
the antibody treatment,
as was agreed upon
by both North and South Korea,
when he disappeared
along with his daughter.
Some organizations accused
the South Korean government
of putting on a show
in order to cripple
the North Korean infrastructure,
and warned that demonstrations
demanding the whereabouts of Dr. Jung
and his daughter,
as well as their return to North Korea,
would take place nationwide.
[man winces]
[newscaster] Opposing organizations
heavily criticized them,
labeling them as pro-North Korean,
accusing them of working
for the North Korean government,
and warned of a counter demonstration.
As a result, police are on high alert
to keep the situation
from getting violent--
-[gun fires]
-[grunts]
[suspenseful music playing]
[agent] Who are you?
Where is Dr. Jung Byeong-ho?
Doctor? Who is that person?
Where did you get this?
Where is Dr. Jung Byeong-ho?
Why are you asking me this?
Watch this.
Dr. Jung is with me at the moment.
If you come to the Possess Motel room 605
in Yeongdeungpo market,
you can meet him.
-[agent 1] This is what you sent.
-[panting]
[man] The man in this video
is me? [breathing shakily]
[agent 2] What have you done
to the back of your head?
[man grunts]
Before we blast your head off,
answer me correctly!
[man] I can't remember anything.
I can't even remember my name. [pants]
[breathing shakily]
-[agent 1] Whose blood is this?
-[breathes shakily]
[suspenseful music playing]
[phone ringing]
[ringing continues]
[agent 2] Answer the phone.
Answer the phone, now!
-[phone continues ringing]
-[man breathing heavily]
[continues ringing]
Hello?
[woman on phone] Your name is Carter.
"Carter"?
What is "Carter"?
[woman] I'd like to speak
with the person behind you.
Could you please put them on the phone?
She'd like to… to speak with you.
[agent 1] Answer.
[suspenseful music playing]
Who is this?
-[explodes]
-[agents shout]
[groans]
[high-pitched whine]
[grunting]
[electronic whine]
[grunting, panting]
[woman] We're going to blow up
this room in 20 seconds.
[grunting]
[woman] That will lure in
the rest of their forces.
[panting]
Who are you? How are you talking to me?
[agent 3] What happened?
[agent 4] What the hell is
this guy rambling on about?
[woman] There is a device implanted
in your ear.
-You are the only one who can hear me.
-[beeping]
Jump out of the window
to get to the next building.
Please trust me, if you want to live.
Ten seconds left.
Ten, nine, eight, seven,
six, five…
[bomb exploding]
[Carter panting]
[woman on earpiece] Carter.
Carter, are you okay?
[Carter] What is this place?
[woman] What is it that you're looking at?
-So you're Korean then?
-[woman] Is that what matters right now?
Listen to me if you want to live.
Sir, help me. Wait.
These assholes are completely insane.
[coughing]
[woman] Don't worry
about the people there,
just get out of that building quickly.
Who are you?
Me?
What, we introducing ourselves now?
I didn't mean you.
When they arrive, you'll die before
you can get your questions answered.
[Carter] Who are "they"?
Why don't you tell me
who the hell you are first, huh?
[woman] CIA.
[Carter] "CIA"?
CIA? So you're here now,
to save me, right?
-The CIA?
-I thought that I was a goner.
[in Japanese]
Are we sure we got the right guy?
-Sorry.
-What are you doing?
Wait. Come on. Murder these bastards!
Hey, what are you waiting for, huh?
-No, that's not me.
-[woman sobbing]
[sobbing]
[water sloshing]
[mystical music playing]
[music intensifies]
[Carter breathing anxiously]
[tense music playing]
[yelling]
[grunting]
[gangster 1 in Japanese] Hold him!
[groaning]
[gangster 2] Kill!
[grunting]
[all yelling]
[knife swishing]
[yelling]
-[knife swishing]
-[grunting]
[screams]
-[grunts]
-[screams]
[all yelling]
-[grunting]
-[glass shattering]
[all yelling]
[screaming]
[Carter grunting]
[grunting]
Yah!
-[yells]
-[grunts]
-[grunting]
-[screaming]
[screaming]
[grunting]
[yells]
-[knife swishing]
-[grunting]
[grunting]
[yelps]
-[yelling]
-[grunting]
[panting]
[screaming]
[yelling]
[body hits the floor]
[panting]
[gangsters moaning in pain]
[all moaning in pain]
-[in Japanese] Over there!
-Kill him!
[gun fires]
[gangster] Over there!
-[gun fires]
-[gangsters groaning]
[gun firing]
-[bullet ricocheting]
-[glass shatters]
[Carter panting]
-[gangster 1] He's going down!
-[gangster 2] Get him!
-[door opens]
-[gangster grunts]
-[yelling]
-[Carter grunting]
[yelling]
[grunting]
[gangster 3] Hyah! [grunts]
-[blood splattering]
-Hyah!
-[grunting]
-[yells]
-[yelling]
[grunting]
-[yelps]
-[glass shattering]
[yelling]
[grunting]
[screaming]
[screams]
-[people murmuring]
-[woman screaming]
[grunting]
[gun firing]
[people panicking]
[man in English]
There he is! Get him! We want him alive!
[woman] The market is right in front
of you. Go in that direction.
[frantic music playing]
[panting]
[woman 2] The other side!
Go out the other side
of the market and turn left.
[frantic music continues]
[yelps]
What in the world…
[music continues]
[Carter] Someone's on my tail.
[woman] 50 meters in front of you,
you'll see a Papa John's motorcycle.
Use it to escape.
[agent 1] Stop that man!
He's getting on a bike!
Stop him! Stop him! Cut him off!
[crashing]
Move!
He's going down! Get him!
-[tires screeching]
-[horn blaring]
[tires screeching]
[frantic music continues]
[brakes squealing]
[tires screeching]
[people screaming]
-[glass shattering]
-[woman screaming]
[people screaming]
[screaming]
[yelps]
[tires screeching]
[frantic music continues]
[people screaming]
[engine revving]
[ties squealing]
[grunts]
[tires screeching]
-[grunts]
-[people scream]
[panting]
-[grunting]
-[people gasping, whimpering]
[grunting]
[agent grunting]
-[grunts]
-[neck cracks]
[panting]
[woman on earpiece] Carter.
Go to the back door of the clothing shop.
[women screaming]
[gasps]
Call the police!
Please, please, come on, hurry.
-Come on, hurry. Please.
-What do I say?
[women gasping]
Yes, I'm at a clothing store.
A strange man…
[gasps]
[woman on earpiece]
You'll find a staircase
at the end of the left passage.
Go upstairs.
[Carter] How do you know all this?
[woman] I can get
the security camera information
and the blind spots from your earpiece,
which can detect heat signatures
in your fifty-meter radius.
[grunts, pants]
[gasps]
[monitor beeping]
[tense music playing]
-[coughs]
-[monitor alarm blaring]
[woman on earpiece] Carter!
A target with a CIA frequency
is approaching.
[coughing]
[woman] Eliminate him
and secure his device.
-[dramatic whoosh]
-[grunts]
[grunting]
[both grunting]
[grunts]
[grunts, pants]
[woman] The CIA is all over the place.
Hide somewhere, now.
[grunting]
[woman] Secure the device on his wrist.
We're going to backtrace their hideout.
"Backtrace"?
[woman] There's a car approaching
at the end of the alley.
Get in the car and hand over the device.
Tell me why the CIA is chasing me.
[woman] There's a lethal bomb
planted in your mouth.
It has blast radius of ten meters.
If you refuse to work with us,
it will activate.
License plate 4566.
Your questions will be answered
once you get into the car.
And why would I get in that car?
Tell me, now.
[woman] Then you give us no choice.
You must be terminated.
I have the detonator here in my hand.
[Carter panting]
[woman] The car is approaching.
Move it. And hurry.
[tense music playing]
[woman] Is Hye-won doing well in class?
[indistinct chatter]
DAEHAN TAEKWONDO
-[woman] Drive! Drive!
-[agent] Over there!
[tires screeching]
-[engine revving]
-[grunts]
You have the device?
-Hack it.
-Right. I'll start tracing them.
Choi Yu-jin, NIS.
Strategic relations with North Korea.
And the woman talking in my ear,
she on your side?
I'm Han Jung Hee.
I work for
the International Liaison Department
of the Labor Party in North Korea.
We are currently working with South Korea
to create a treatment for the DMZ Virus.
[Yu-jin] These are North Koreans
who have been infected by the DMZ Virus.
The infected
are overwhelmingly strong and violent.
Some have been discovered
to even be able to use tools or weapons.
All of South Korea's army is at the DMZ,
holding off the infected,
but every day is precarious.
[Jung Hee] In North Korea, we have secured
a hundred million anthrax vaccines
needed to produce the treatment,
as well as a large scale assembly line,
so that Dr. Jung's research
can be carried out smoothly.
That's the reason we tried to bring
Dr. Jung and his daughter, Jung Ha-na,
to the North
for the completion of the project.
Daughter?
Dr. Jung's daughter was infected
by a field rat
while they were living out in Paju.
He was able to cure his own daughter,
and started studying her antibodies
to find a treatment.
However, due to an abnormal increase
in thromboplastin,
an enzyme that coagulates blood
once it leaves the body,
her antibodies were destroyed in seconds.
That's why we were heading to
the Sinuiju Chemical Weapons Institute,
for Ha-na's blood.
[Jung Hee] However, Ha-na was kidnapped
on her way to North Korea
by an agent from A9,
a secret organization in the CIA,.
Your mission is to find Ha-na
and bring her to North Korea.
You're the one who suggested this mission.
It was your idea.
Why would I?
[Jung Hee] You commanded us
to block the memory center in your brain.
Am I your commander?
[Jung Hee] I suppose you'll return
to your position
after the mission is finished.
Why would I erase my memory,
and give up my rank?
[Jung Hee] You used to be
a CIA agent from South Korea,
but you disguised yourself as a reporter
and entered North Korea.
You became a hero to our people.
You were a hero to South Korea.
However, the North Korean government was
suspicious that you were an American spy
and assigned a woman
to keep a close eye on you.
The two of you fell in love,
and even got married.
And then, you had a daughter.
This woman and I?
[Yu-jin] But your wife died
from the DMZ Virus,
and your daughter, Yoon Hee,
also got infected
and is now imprisoned
in the research facility in Sinuiju.
[beeps]
[Carter on video] This is a good shot.
Look over here.
Yoon Hee.
[somber music playing]
Yoon Hee!
[Yoon Hee] Dad? Dad?
Dad… [sobbing]
-[sobbing] …Dad.
-[Carter] Yoon Hee.
[Yoon Hee sobbing]
[Jung Hee] That scar
on the back of your hand
is from the burn that you got that night.
The weapons you need
for the infiltration are in here.
Now you can do what Han Jung Hee says
until the assignment is complete.
[Jung Hee] You need to save Ha-na
so that your daughter,
Lee Yun Hui, might live.
-[engine revving]
-[tires screeching]
[contemplative music playing]
[Jung Hee] Go to the rooftop.
Ha-na is being held in the building
across from this one.
[music continues]
[tires screeching]
Check the weapons in the bag
and put them on.
[unzipping]
We must move Ha-na today
if we want to save your daughter's life.
She doesn't have much time left.
The majority of those infected
die just under 13 days.
Today is the 13th day
since your daughter was infected.
How do I know
that child is really my daughter?
[Jung Hee] When you get your memory back,
and your daughter is dead,
who will you blame?
[action music playing]
[panting]
Go through the door to your right
and move to the edge of the rooftop.
I've hacked the communication channels
of the CIA agents in the building.
I'm getting their whereabouts now.
[agent 1 on radio] Negative, sir.
We're still working on
establishing the identity of the subject.
[agent 2] Bullshit! Get the geeks
at Langley on it if you have to.
I can't do shit
until we have actual evidence
that the North is on the move.
[Jung Hee] The agents are gathered in
the motel you were in. Now is the chance.
[tense music playing]
[grunts]
[whizzing]
[whirring]
FLORAL SUPPLIES WHOLESALE MARKET
[grunts, pants]
[Jung Hee] The elevator control room is
through the door in front of you.
Move toward it.
[action music continues]
I'm detecting the heat signature
of one adult
near the elevator on the ninth floor
and two on the seventh floor.
This mall looks out of business.
[Jung Hee] It's the perfect place
for the CIA to set up a temporary base.
The agents that were sent to the motel
are on their way back. Hurry.
And Ha-na?
[Jung Hee] I'm detecting
the heat signature.
I'm detecting her on the sixth floor.
[action music continues]
[gun firing]
[grunts]
[Carter grunts]
[Jung Hee] Ha-na will be in the playroom
once you go through the emergency exit.
The heat signatures
near the entrance are targets.
EMERGENCY EXIT
[gun fires]
[footsteps treading]
[suspenseful music playing]
Who are you? Why are you here?
Stay back! Stay away from me!
[Carter] Ha-na? You're Ha-na, right?
-Listen, I'm--
-Stay back I said!
[panting]
What should I do?
[Jung Hee] Hand her the phone.
[Carter panting]
Here, answer it.
I'll stay over here. Hmm?
[phone buzzing]
Um, hello?
Dad? Dad, please, where are you?
Yeah.
Okay.
Dad, can I trust this man?
Okay, I'll do that.
Okay.
[phone beeps]
Are you all right?
-Yes.
-Let's go find your dad.
How though? How do we get out of here?
[suspenseful music playing]
[glass shatters]
[music continues]
-[hissing]
-[agent 1] Get back! Get back!
[all coughing]
[coughing continues]
[tense music playing]
[light flickering]
[Carter panting]
[breathing deeply]
[tense music playing]
You are a hard man to find, Mr. Lee.
Carter Lee.
That is your name, isn't it?
Oh, we're playing that game now.
That's fine.
Fortunately for us, I have a shit-ton
of computer geeks back at Langley
who get a boner whenever I ask
them to dig up some shit on people.
[chuckles]
Between you and me,
they're probably a bunch
of introverted perverts who
couldn't do four push-ups
to save their life. But, uh,
they get the job done. So, you know,
what are you gonna to do?
All right, let's see here.
"Carter Lee. Born in 1986.
Jamsil, South Korea."
"Immigrated to New York at age 11."
Blah, blah, blah.
Some more boring shit.
Oh, damn!
You went to Sornell?
My cousin went there!
Yeah! [chuckles]
He was a real piece of shit.
[chuckles softly]
Oh, okay, here we go.
2014, you traveled to North Korea
as a journalist and, uh…
What?
You become
a naturalized citizen of the DPRK?
[gasps] Oh!
I bet it was
all of that socialist bullshit
they taught you back at Sornell.
Am I right? Huh?
A real hero of the people.
Yeah.
[inhales deeply] So,
here's the thing I don't understand,
and, uh, maybe you can help me out this.
What the fuck
are you doing back in South Korea?
And more importantly,
why are you fucking up my shit?
[light flickering]
All right. [chuckles, inhales]
So check this out, man. I…
I actually don't give a fuck about you.
I-- I really don't.
Just tell me who you're working for.
And, uh… we'll call it a day.
Huh?
Is it the North?
Is it the South?
Come on. You can tell Smith Hyeong.
The North or the South.
What does it matter?
[Smith] Oh, shit.
[laughing] You can talk!
I'm sorry. I'm sorry. Please, continue.
At least they aren't the ones
watching people die from the virus.
And treating it as an opportunity.
[Smith] So you're saying
the United States…
You think those 300,000
pissed off Koreans out there,
feel the same way?
I don't know,
I think they're pretty convinced
that this is all a fabricated scheme
formed by the South Korean government!
"Fabricated"?
Didn't you create that rumor
to incite a riot?
"Rumor"?
[scoffs] Us?
[laughs]
[inhales deeply] Oh, wow.
Carter.
The things they led you to believe…
Have you ever considered the possibility
that it could be
even more blinding
of the truth?
The real truth?
[agent] Sir!
What is it?
The CCTV results came in.
The movement of Carter Lee matches
that of former CIA Agent Michael Bane
by 87%.
Michael Bane…
Wasn't he KIA in Syria
in your last deployment together?
Yes, sir.
They told us he was dead,
but none of us had
actual eyes on his remains.
[suspenseful music playing]
[groans] The fuck are you doing?
BD-7…
That's how
they successfully wiped his memory.
Maybe.
But I don't think they fully reconstructed
the new one quite yet.
The eyes…
You can change the face,
but not the eyes.
And they never lie.
Is this why you rushed back to Korea?
We'll have the answers
once we've run the DNA lab, sir.
[inhales deeply]
The commies are getting cute. [sighs]
Run it.
Sir.
What the hell's going on?
Hang tight, hero.
Who knows?
Maybe the results will tell me
that you're not as useless as I thought.
[agent 2 on radio] Sir! There's a signal
coming from the subject's body.
Scan it.
[Jung Hee] Carter!
I need to cut communication
from your ear piece for a moment
and use the signal in your molar
as a decoy.
[device whirring]
Picking up a strange signal
coming from his molar, sir.
What the fuck are you waiting on?
Take it out!
[grunts] Get off me! Get off!
[grunts]
[Jung Hee] Just open your mouth.
[grunting]
[groans]
The molar will detonate in five seconds.
-[panting]
-[exploding]
[grunting]
-[grunting]
-[Ha-na screams]
-[exploding]
-[agents yell]
-[tense music playing]
-[Carter panting]
[light flickering]
Get on my back.
[panting]
Hold tightly onto me.
[tense music continues]
[music intensifies]
-[grunting]
-[Ha-na grunting]
-[Carter] Ha-na!
-[screams, grunts]
-Mister, help!
-Ha-na, hang on just a second!
[grunting]
[yells]
[grunts]
[panting]
-[grunting]
-[agent yelps, grunts]
[Ha-na] Mister, help!
[screams]
[Carter grunts, pants]
Are you okay?
Yes, I'm okay.
Hey, are you all right?
-What are you doing? This is my work van--
-[gun fires]
-[Ha-na screams]
-[man whimpers]
[gun firing]
-[grunts]
-[engine starts]
[van speeding away]
-Go, go, go!
-He's taking off!
[agent] Get him!
[thrilling music playing]
[tires screeching]
[traditional dance music playing]
[man] Repatriate Dr. Jung to North Korea!
[demonstrators] Repatriate! Repatriate!
[woman] We know the US is behind all this!
[demonstrators] We know! We know!
[man] Repatriate Dr. Jung to North Korea!
[demonstrators] Repatriate! Repatriate!
[woman] We know the US is behind all this!
[demonstrators] We know! We know!
[man] Repatriate Dr. Jung to North Korea!
[demonstrators] Repatriate! Repatriate!
Ha-na, what's wrong?
[demonstrators] We know! We know!
[Carter] Ha-na! Ha-na!
[Ha-na] Dad.
Dad!
[demonstrators] To North Korea!
To North Korea!
[Ha-na] Dad!
[demonstrators] We know! We know!
[panting]
[Dr. Jung] Ha-na.
Do you know how worried I've been?
[panting]
[Dr. Jung] Where have you been?
-Huh?
-[Carter] Ha-na. What's wrong?
[demonstrators] We know! We know!
My dad is over there…
But that's not me.
He's with some other girl…
[demonstrators] Repatriate! Repatriate!
[woman] We know the US is behind all this!
[demonstrators] We know! We know!
But why are people wearing masks
of me and my dad?
[demonstrators] Repatriate! Repatriate!
Well, it's because
they want you to stay safe.
[demonstrators] We know! We know!
[Carter] Should we put them on too?
[demonstrators] Repatriate! Repatriate!
[woman] We know the US is behind all this!
We know! We know!
[thunder rumbling]
[newscaster] We bring you breaking news.
Dr. Jung, who had been missing until now,
has been confirmed to be in Sinuiju.
We've just received a video
showing Dr. Jung himself.
Let us take a look.
[Dr. Jung] Hello. I am Jung Byeong-ho.
And I have arrived safely to Sinuiju,
thanks to the North
and South Korean governments.
I have also spoken to my daughter
on the phone moments ago
and I plan to start developing a cure
as soon as possible…
EXCLUSIVE INTERVIEW WITH JUNG BYEONG-HO
once I make it to
the Sinuiju Institute as planned.
Also, I have heard rumors
that the South Korean government
is attempting to destroy the North
right now.
However, I assure you it is not true.
Please do not be misled.
[newscaster] That was a video of Dr. Jung
sent directly from Sinuiju.
We will be reporting the rest
on our regular scheduled news. Thank you.
[thunder rumbling]
[thunder crashing]
This should be good enough.
One year anniversary song.
Three, two, one.
-No! He can't.
-What?
-You're terrible at writing songs.
-Yeah, I can't. [laughs]
Wait, try again…
[Jung Hee] Carter, why did you stop?
Ha-na is a little tired.
-I'm fine--
-Shh.
[Jung Hee] The van is approaching
across the street. Hurry.
[suspenseful music playing]
[music continues]
[tires screeching]
DAEHAN TAEKWONDO
[Yu-jin] What?
Carter is heading towards the bus
with Ha-na!
[Jung Hee] Carter. Where are you going?
Follow my instructions.
I'm detecting the movements
of CIA agents nearby.
Carter! Why are you getting on a bus
all of a sudden?
Get off the bus!
Listen to my instructions. Carter!
I think the CIA has caught on to your van.
[Jung Hee] If you don't follow my orders,
you and your daughter will both-
-[electronic warble and whine]
-[groans]
[grunts]
[panting]
I've blocked the signal
to the device in your ear, Mich…
Agent Bane.
Why are you calling me Michael Bane?
It's time you tell me who you really are.
Someone who knows you better
than that voice in your ear.
Yeah? What makes you so sure?
[exhales sharply]
There was a time
where we faced life and death, together.
I'm on your side, Mike. I always was.
My side?
Your men just tried to kill me back there.
And you expect me
to believe that you're on my side?
You really don't remember us?
[scoffs]
I still see you…
In your eyes, I…
I just know you're still there.
I just know it's you.
[breathes deeply]
[scoffs] Never mind.
[sniffles]
It doesn't matter
if you remember me or not.
The DNA test will prove
that you're Michael Bane.
And until then,
our agency will continue to hunt you down.
You have to trust me
if you want to survive.
Yeah?
I've been hearing that a lot lately.
Fine. It's time you know
who they really are.
[man on earpiece] What's going on?
You still can't get a signal to Carter?
[Jung Hee] Someone's blocking
the communications channel.
First, let me identify the woman
who approached Carter.
[man 2] The South is manipulating
the traffic lights.
The bus will stop 50 meters ahead
for one minute.
-Then we will be in range for the shot.
-[man] Take her down.
[Jung Hee] We can identify her first,
there'll be time to take her out after.
[man] Fire!
[gun fires]
[grunts, gasps]
Run, Mike. Run before my men get here.
-[horn honks]
-[female agent panting]
[passenger 1] Hurry, hurry, hurry, hurry!
[passenger 2] She got shot!
[whimpering] Call an ambulance!
[Carter grunting]
[tense music playing]
[panting]
-[engine revving]
-[Ha-na] Mister!
-[Carter grunts]
-[tires squealing]
[frantic music playing]
[grunting]
[tires screeching]
[music continues]
-[tires screeching]
-[Ha-na screaming]
[tires squealing]
-[tires screeching]
-[horn blaring]
[tires screeching]
[Ha-na screaming]
[grunts]
[tires screeching]
Hold on tight! Careful!
[screams]
[horn blaring]
[groaning]
[grunting]
-[gun fires]
-[tires screeching]
[frantic music continues]
[Carter grunting]
[panting]
[Ha-na screaming]
-[gun fires]
-[grunting]
[grunting, panting]
[grunting]
[grunts]
[pants, grunts]
[female agent] We all saw the lab results!
Hold your fire!
That's Michael Bane!
[agent] It doesn't matter who he is.
He's gone rogue.
We have to take him out.
[female agent] It's not his fault.
He's just being used by the people
that are really pulling the strings.
[agent] Yeah, well, that puppet
is about to kill Paul!
Requesting permission to engage.
[female agent] Please, sir, don't do this.
[Smith] Take the shot.
-[grunts]
-[gun fires]
-[firing continues]
-[Paul groans]
-[Carter grunts]
-[gun firing]
[grunting]
[gun firing]
[yells, grunts]
[grunting]
-[knife swishing]
-[groaning]
[grunting]
[Ha-na screaming]
[Ha-na] Mister, please help me!
Mister!
[dramatic music plays in slow motion]
[dramatic music playing]
[engine revving]
[tires screeching]
[agent] Use the bus, block him!
[tires squealing]
[gun firing]
-[brakes squealing]
-[crashing]
[tires screeching]
[motorbike revving]
[dramatic music playing]
-[gun firing]
-[tires screeching]
-[grunting]
[grunting]
[tires screeching]
[agent 1] Hold your fire!
Checking DNA now.
[agent 2] Plan B. Surround him.
[grunting]
-[stabbing]
-[blood squirting]
[grunting]
-[tires screeching]
-[gun fires]
[explodes]
-[thuds]
-[water splashing]
[solemn music playing]
[helicopter whirring]
[Jung Hee] There is an emergency
military airstrip at the end of the road.
A plane is waiting there
to take you to North Korea.
My name is Kim Dong-gyu, Director
of North Korean Relations at the NIS.
I am responsible
for getting you to North Korea safely.
[Jung Hee] We opened a communications
channel in the South as well.
You've done well.
Hey, Jung Hee?
I don't think he trusts me. [chuckles]
[Jung Hee] Director Kim will be
ensuring your safety during the flight.
Come on. Let's board.
The reporters will hassle you.
Don't say a thing.
Don't look at them either.
Keep looking forward.
Even your slightest movement, Agent Lee,
may put this country
could put Dr. Jung and South Korea
in a dangerous spot.
[reporters clamoring]
[reporter] Is it true that Ha-na's…
We'll be flying with US reporters.
Reporters will be on board?
Yes, that way,
the entire world will be watching us.
It'll keep the US government
from acting so reckless.
[reporter] How did you find her?
Please cooperate, as this was a choice
to ensure our safe arrival.
Jung Ha-na,
kidnapped daughter of Dr. Jung Byeong-ho,
reappeared today.
Now, the South Korean government
gave no statement
regarding the kidnapping itself,
merely making a statement that reuniting
the doctor with his daughter
is of the utmost priority.
We will keep you updated
on further developments in this story,
which will hopefully result
in Ha-na's safe return to North Korea.
[Director Kim] Hey now,
you shouldn't smoke with a child on board.
[official] Hey, look,
there's no need to be so uptight.
[laughs]
[inhales deeply] You will be staying here
as we make our way to North Korea.
Here, this way.
[tense music playing]
Hey, you gotta be Ha-na.
Ha-na.
Come on, all right?
To start, you should both see our medic.
TREATMENT ROOM
Hello. Welcome.
If you'll remove that,
we can start the treatment.
You can take that seat.
The plane is taking off soon.
[reporter] Excuse me,
we have an interview.
-[agent] After the treatment.
-Well, we'll do the interview later.
[Director Kim] Sorry, later.
You both can change
once your injuries are mended.
Okay. Disinfect it.
Don't worry. It won't hurt anymore, okay?
Mister, are you okay?
I'm okay.
Are you okay?
I'm okay too.
[Carter] Hmm.
Why is your hand like that?
I can't remember.
I think I was with my daughter.
Well, um, aren't you remembering now?
When I see this scar on my hand,
it's as if I can hear a child crying.
Though, she might not
make it through today.
My daughter, that is.
What's your daughter's name?
Yoon Hee.
"Yoon Hee."
But I'm here, so it'll work out.
I'm the cure, right? A human cure.
[laughs]
[man] All right, the treatment is done.
Excellent. Thank you.
All right. Why don't you put these on?
Ha-na, you should get changed as well,
after Mr. Carter is done. [chuckles]
Once you arrive in North Korea,
your mission will be finished.
I sincerely hope
that the cure is completed in time,
so that your child can be saved.
Was this mission really my choice?
So that I could save my daughter?
[Director Kim] You'll get an answer
to that question
once your mission is complete.
Until then, don't let down your guard.
Remember this.
there may even be individuals
on this plane who are after Ha-na.
[Carter] Didn't you say
that the US can't interfere anymore?
[Jung Hee] We have reason to believe
that the CIA may have ordered
other forces to move in on Ha-na.
It's possible North-Korean personnel
may be involved, wanting to start a coup.
[Carter sighs] The CIA contacting
the spy organization makes sense,
but what do you mean
by a coup within North Korea?
Well, we suspect
the virus may have been spread,
by those who want
the current regime to collapse.
Until Ha-na is safely reunited
with her father Dr. Jung,
don't trust anybody.
Don't even trust me. [scoffs]
-[loud rumble]
-[yelps]
[clattering]
-[Carter] What's going on?
-Don't worry. I'll go investigate.
[breathes deeply]
-What's going on?
-We've lost contact with the cockpit.
What?
[frantic music playing]
-[agent] Director Kim, what's going on?
-[reporter] Is there a problem?
Hurry, we need a medic!
What happened?
They both just collapsed.
But they just drank coffee.
Coffee?
Sir, I didn't do it.
Look, I brought the coffee
but that was it.
[suspenseful music playing]
No, you can't! Who else can fly the plane?
Look at his bloodshot eyes.
This plane's going down in ten minutes
if it's a mutated variant.
What do you think you're doing?
Director Kim tried to kill
Comrade Pilot and Comrade Assistant Pilot.
If we don't kill them, we will all die!
Everyone, calm down.
First we'll confirm they're infected.
Medic!
[tense music playing]
[device beeps]
[official] How does it look?
Technically,
in normal situations, this level
wouldn't be considered high enough,
but considering
the altitude and cabin pressure,
technically, this is an infection.
[Director Kim]
So, are they infected or not?
Give us more time to observe it.
At least give us five minutes
to get a proper reading.
What's the difference
in killing them now or then?
Hang on. But his hair roots are strong.
Don't you know it's too late
once the hair starts falling out?
The protocol states that
reading times are to be observed.
If anything happens in the meantime,
they will instantly be shot.
[engine powering down]
-[woman gasps]
-[alarm sounding]
[official] Open the blinds in the cabin!
The blinds, they aren't working.
Why is the medical room
emergency lights off?
Out of my way.
-Move!
-[official] Director Kim!
Director Kim, what's the situation?
Due to what felt like extreme turbulence,
we appear to have lost power on board.
Now, that is an extremely…
[Jung Hee] Carter.
Only you can hear what I'm saying.
In the cargo compartment,
I am sensing the heat signatures
of what appear to be an adult and Ha-na.
-The cargo compartment?
-[Jung Hee] You need to head there.
-[agent] Let's go.
-[man] This is why South Korean bastards…
-You can never trust them.
-[agent] Ha-na!
CARGO COMPARTMENT
[suspenseful music playing]
CABIN
[door closes]
Ha-na. Are you okay? Who did this?
-[grunts]
-[yells]
-[grunting]
-[groaning]
-Why are you doing this?
-[laughs]
Your eyes really say
that you don't remember anything.
[panting]
-What?
-Yeah. Yeah.
If you don't remember anything,
at least you'll be at peace
when you die, right?
[grunting]
-[gun fires]
-[groans, screams in pain]
[grunts, pants]
-[groaning]
-Carter.
[man] Director Kim.
Why… Why are you doing this?
Ri Cheol Ju, you son of a bitch!
Ha-na, are you all right?
-[Ha-na] Yes.
-Don't move!
[Cheol Ju gasps]
Who is it?
Who's the head of the North Korean coup?
Who spread this virus? Who created it!?
[laughs]
Do you really think North Korea would
make this mess just to die
and when we don't even have a vaccine yet?
[laughs]
But have you considered that maybe,
it's the South that wanted the coup?
[laughs]
I guess you,
are just another facet of this
to make it more interesting.
Now that's enough of your bullshit.
Just answer me.
Who is it?
Lee Dong Jin?
Han Seol Ho?
Kim Jong Hyeok?
[Cheol Ju laughs]
Director Kim.
You're embarrassing yourself,
You believe those stereotypes, huh?
You think I have loyalty to the North?
What, 'cause I'm from North Korea?
Is that it then?
[laughs]
What?
Do you think there's only one spy
like him in the North?
-[laughs]
-Ri Cheol Ju, you asshole!
Are you working with the United States?
[Cheol Ju laughs]
[grunts]
Listen carefully.
Up there in the North,
the people call South Korea
an American colony.
The thing is,
after having met these Americans,
it looks like being on their side,
is more than worth it for me.
America.
Its freedom and equality.
A place with wealth
and all its opportunity.
Considering all of that!
Even if I live one day!
I'll live free, like a human!
Do you get that, Director?
Do you? [sobs]
[Director Kim] Die, you son of a bitch!
[gun fires]
[grunting]
-[grunts]
-[yells]
[groans]
[grunting]
-[gun fires]
-[panting]
[grunting]
[pants]
[screams]
Ha-na, get out of here.
-Mister.
-[Cheol Ju grunting]
-Run fast and get help.
-[screams]
-Hurry up! Be quick! [grunting]
-[screaming]
[grunting]
-[door closes]
-[gasps]
[panting]
[foreboding music playing]
[alarm blaring]
[panting]
-What's going on here?
-Huh?
Wasn't that an explosion?
-The cockpit door won't open.
-What?
Ha-na!
-Ha-na. You all right?
-Why were you in there?
Have you been down there this whole time?
What were you doing in there?
Hey, wait a sec.
Director Kim went that way. Was he there?
He's dead.
The North Korean guy…
he killed Mr. Kim.
What's going on? What are you people
trying to pull over here?
We… We don't know anything!
Who was it? Who killed Director Kim?
Could you recognize their face?
-[agent] It's okay.
-[breathing shakily]
[footsteps approaching]
[gasps] It was that man!
[panting]
Did you kill Director Kim? Huh?
Answer the question!
[sobbing]
Yes, I did.
It was me.
Listen, Director Kim was just a CIA spy
that was planted here.
He was trying to take Ha-na away.
So I did it. I killed him. [sobs]
I knew those South Korean bastards
would do this!
They're working with the CIA.
Those bastards!
Are you really going to listen
to this bastard?
Hey, hey, hey. Whoa! Calm down, okay?
Put the guns away for a second.
You can't just accept
whatever this guy is trying to say.
Ask Ha-na.
Is that true, Ha-na?
Did Director Kim take you?
[breathing heavily]
[loud clank]
[eerie music playing]
[official] Oh, yes, Comrade Sun Hwa.
Are you all right?
How are the pilot and the co-pilot doing?
They are…
doing just fine.
[gun firing]
[clamoring]
[reporter] He's choking her.
One of the North Koreans is choking Ha-na.
[all screaming]
He's… He's covering himself in her blood.
[yells]
[reporter] It's Ha-na's blood.
The infected aren't attacking him
because of her blood.
[grunting]
[yelling]
[panicked screams]
[whimpering, screaming]
[people snarling]
[panting]
[grunting]
[screaming, grunting]
[wind whooshing]
[reporter screaming]
[grunting]
[panting]
[grunting, panting]
[groans, pants]
Ah! This is so exciting.
Hey. Look at you trying to survive.
This is some thrill, huh?
Looks like the people's hero,
is just a human when faced with death.
[laughs]
Get ready!
[man on radio]
Moving to an estimated landing point
at 40 degrees latitude
and 124 degrees longitude.
[grunts]
[grunting]
[exploding]
[dramatic music playing]
[grunting]
-[gun fires]
-[grunting]
[action music playing]
[guns firing]
[Ha-na screams]
[gun firing]
[Ha-na grunts]
[Ha-na screams]
[grunts]
[whooshing]
-Ha-na, are you all right?
-[Ha-na] Yes.
-[grunts]
-[pigs squealing]
[action music continues]
[gun fires]
[man] Kill the man
and catch the girl alive!
[music continues]
[gun firing]
-[pigs snorting]
-[Carter grunts]
Somebody is on my tail!
[Jung Hee on earpiece]
They're probably working with Ri Cheol Ju.
-[gun fires]
-[grunts]
[Jung Hee] Carter!
Carter, are you all right?
Answer me. Carter!
[music continues]
[pig squealing]
[grunts]
[grunting]
Ha-na, grab the steering wheel! Go!
[Ha-na] Okay.
[grunting]
[yells]
[grunts]
[pig squealing]
[man] Shoot the wheel!
[gun firing]
[grunts]
[grunting]
[yells]
[shouts]
[Carter grunts]
-[yells, grunts]
-[Carter grunts]
[breathing frantically]
[gun firing]
[pigs squealing]
[Carter grunting]
[Ha-na grunts]
-[pig squeals]
-[grunts]
[grunts] Shit!
I'm out of bullets!
Move the car closer! Faster! More! More!
[grunting]
[panting, grunting]
[grunts]
[tires screeching]
[yells]
[grunts, pants]
[grunts]
Where do I go now?
[Jung Hee] If you follow the valley down
about 20 meters,
there's a cliff and a rope bridge.
We are moving
to the opposite side now too.
The mission will be complete
once you get there.
Mister.
Here.
[panting]
Let's go.
-Be careful, it's slippery.
-[Ha-na] Okay.
[grunts, pants]
[foreboding music playing]
[gun firing]
[dramatic music playing]
[both panting]
[gun firing]
[Carter panting]
[gun fires]
Here. Get on my back.
I can go on my own.
[panting]
-[panting]
-[frantic music playing]
[infected man yelling]
-[gun fires]
-[grunts]
[snarling]
[gun firing]
[Ha-na screams]
[Carter grunts]
-[grunting]
-[Ha-na panting]
-[gun firing]
-[Ha-na grunting]
[gun firing]
[Ha-na grunts]
-[Carter grunts]
-[Ha-na yelps]
[dramatic music playing]
[gun firing]
[yelling]
[infected people screaming]
[infected man roars]
[Ha-na grunts]
[grunts] Hug my neck
and clasp your hands together!
Don't ever let go!
-[Ha-na] Okay.
-[gun firing]
[Ha-na screams]
[thuds]
[epic music playing]
-[gun firing]
-[snarling]
[gun firing]
[firing continues]
[Carter grunting]
-[gun firing]
-[infected man snarls]
[Carter grunting]
[Jung Hee] Carter!
[Carter panting, grunting]
[panting]
[woman] Are you okay?
Are you Han Jung Hee?
Ha-na, are you okay?
So you're Ha-na. You've done a lot.
Thank you for your hard work.
Now we can leave together.
What exactly are you saying?
Leave together?
[vehicle door opens]
[breathing heavily]
This is simply incredible.
A job well done.
It's a surprise
that you would love a woman
and a daughter that you two had
while you were working undercover. Hmm?
And I applaud you
for putting your life at risk,
to protect your own daughter.
Who are you, huh?
Oh.
I'm Kim Jong Hyeok.
You know, seeing what you're capable of,
you sure don't seem
like you lost your memory.
[laughs]
Stop laughing. I want my memory back.
[breathing shakily]
Go on. Sit down.
Once the device implanted
in your ear is removed,
you'll get your memory back.
[Carter panting]
Trust me. Okay?
-[device whirring]
-[grunts]
[breathing shakily]
[Jung Hee] I'm going to open the stitches.
This will hurt a bit.
-[Carter grunts]
-[Jung Hee yelps]
Mister!
What's going on? Lieutenant General!
-Get up!
-[Ha-na grunts]
-Carter! [gasps]
-[Ha-na] Mister!
-[gasps]
Where are you taking Carter? Tell me.
Look here, Han Jung Hee.
Don't make a scene. And stand down.
But you made us a promise!
We could leave this country
after Carter had finished the mission.
That deal was between you and the party.
I have never made such a promise.
Then what does that mean?
Put her in the car.
[grunts] Let go of me. Let go!
Let go! [grunting]
-[panting]
-[vehicle door opens]
[Jung Hee grunting, panting]
-[door closes]
-[engine starts]
[grunting]
What do you think you're doing with me?
Love.
I always feel sad when I hear that word.
What is it to be so cruel?
Who knew that comrade Han Jung Hee,
the most competent
female comrade in the North,
could now find herself struggling
down in the gutter?
Huh?
Look, just make your point.
I knew it from the first moment,
the virus spread.
This completely rotten country,
all those pricks in South Korea
who only think about money,
and even those arrogant
American imperialist bastards,
can be destroyed in one strike.
It's a once in a lifetime chance
from the heavens.
Wait, are you
the head of the coup in the North?
[Jong Hyeok] Comrade Han.
Listen to me.
Let's create a new world together.
[soldier] Hey, the bastard's awake.
[laughs]
[grunts]
You American traitor.
So you're finally awake.
Where are you taking me?
Just keep quiet,
and your wife will make the decision.
My wife?
If you had never shown up here,
then the Comrade First Lieutenant Han
who I once loved
just might have been my wife.
[laughing]
Go on.
[lock clicks]
[door opens]
Get out.
[breathing shakily]
Move it, pal. What are you looking at?
[vehicle beeping]
Enjoy that breath. It'll be your last.
Who knows, huh?
You might walk away a North Korean hero
and ex spy agent,
or you might become barbecue in this fire.
Don't worry though, it'll be decided soon.
Comrade hero,
if you've been good to your wife,
you might live.
[cackles]
[tense music playing]
[dramatic music playing]
[screaming]
[snarling]
[grunting]
[gun firing]
[gun fires]
[panting]
[grunts]
[soldier panting]
Please let me live.
[phone ringing]
[Carter] Pick up the phone.
[ringing continues]
Put it on speaker.
Yeah.
[Jong Hyeok on phone] Where is Carter?
[panting] Waiting to be thrown
into the pit.
-What's the order?
-[Jong Hyeok] Wait a bit longer.
[soldier] Yes, sir.
Kim Jong Hyeok, tell me where he is.
[soldier] He's at, uh, the Sinuiju
Chemical Factory's biochemical facilities
about 1.5 kilometers to the north--
[gun fires]
[grunts]
[suspenseful music playing]
-[gun firing]
-[infected man snarling]
-[grunts]
[door closes]
[engine starts]
[solemn music playing]
[grunts softly]
[solemn music continues]
I'M GOING TO CALL YOU
KEEP ME ON THE PHONE - CARTER
[line ringing]
[Jong Hyeok] You look like
you still haven't decided.
Don't overthink it.
You need to save your family,
Carter, yourself, and your daughter.
I can guarantee their safety.
Let us go, like the party had promised.
I don't care what you do here,
what you do with North Korea.
Well, maybe you should care.
For instance,
if you two work with the Americans
and were to say all sorts of bullshit
to the entire world,
how will I look?
I'll most likely get furious
and drag you all here again
to bury you all deep within
that anthrax incinerator
But then again… [sighs]
…if Carter Lee,
who saved the North from the virus,
were to stand with me and my men,
your husband will become a new idol
in uniting all of North Korea.
[scoffs]
Idol, huh?
You just want a puppet, don't you,
who will do as you please?
Look, if it means he survives
then being a puppet is a small price.
Am I wrong?
Lieutenant General.
As I'm looking at you, threatening me
that you'll kill my husband,
I'm not seeing
any new world
for the North Korean people.
I was certain you'd been blinded by a man,
but you've been blinded
to your immediate future as well.
I can't plan the future
of the People's Republic
with someone who's as blind as you are.
[gun firing]
-[soldier] Shoot him!
-[gun fires]
[guns firing]
[frantic music playing]
[grunting]
[gun firing]
[panting]
[snarling]
[screaming]
-[soldier 1 screaming]
-[grunting]
[snarling]
[soldier 2 screaming]
-[gun firing]
-[grunts]
-[grunting]
-Get down!
-[snarling]
[gun firing]
[Jung Hee panting]
This is the room. Yoon Hee is in here.
-[Carter] Where is she?
-Huh? No, where is she?
This has to be the right room.
-[gasps]
-[Yoon Hee snarling]
-[grunts]
-[snarling]
No, don't! [grunts]
-[Carter] This child…
-She's our daughter!
-[Carter] She's our daughter?
-[Jung Hee grunting]
-Carter!
-[grunting]
[grunting]
-[infected man yelling]
-[grunting]
-[Yoon Hee panting]
[grunting]
-[gun fires]
-[grunts]
[infected people moaning]
Mister!
Ha-na.
It's all right.
These people are just researchers.
[Jung Hee] Doctor, our daughter…
[Dr. Jung] You've been infected as well.
The child will be conscious
in about half an hour.
-[door opens]
-[gun firing]
[frantic music playing]
[infected people shouting]
We need to get out of here, now.
-[snarling]
-[gun fires]
[grunts]
[grunts, yells]
[gun fires]
[groaning]
Please save my Ha-na.
The door is locked. [panting]
[grunts]
[gun firing]
[grunting, screaming]
-[gun fires]
-[grunts]
-[gun firing]
-[objects clattering]
-[screaming]
-[infected people grunting]
[grunts]
[Carter] Ha-na, it's me.
Ha-na. Ha-na, let's go.
[panting]
[infected people screaming, snarling]
-[gun firing]
-[glass shatters]
[snarling]
[yelling]
[growling]
[gun fires]
[Jung Hee] Go into the closet
in front of you.
[Carter panting]
[Jung Hee panting]
[vehicle approaching]
[brakes screeching]
-[gun fires]
-[grunts]
[panting]
Give her to me.
[snarling]
[tires screeching]
[guns firing]
-[gun fires]
-[grunts]
[gun fires]
Seven minutes ago, a train operated
by the… the Chinese government
left Ryung Gye for Dandong,
carrying the infected.
Not even the North Korean government
can interfere with that train,
so we need to stop it.
But we need to get your memory back first.
Doctor.
If you open his stitches,
you'll see a device.
If you plug this into it,
his memories will return.
"BD-7."
[grunting]
[grunting, breathing heavily]
[breathes shakily]
[breathing heavily]
-[Jong Hyeok] Do you think it is wise for…
-[Carter] Yoon Hee!
-[Yoon Hee] Dad…
-[Carter] I'll get Ha-na to the North.
Dr. Jung is with me at the moment.
[Jong Hyeok] Yoon Hee's been infected.
Just a bit longer. We're almost there.
[gun fires]
-[groans]
-[Carter] Jung Hee!
-[groans, gasps]
-[crashes]
[grunts, pants]
-[door opens]
-[Carter grunts]
[panting]
[vehicle doors slamming]
The country is falling into ruins
because of the virus.
So do you think it wise
that our Comrade hero of the Republic
is abandoning the country
during a time such as this?
Let us go. I beg you.
Lieutenant General, please.
Just let us go, please.
So you still haven't come
to your senses, Comrade.
Have you forgotten
that having your child
was the party's decision?
Please tell your superiors
if you… if you swear
to release our family,
I'll get Ha-na to the North.
Do you know what you've said?
What it will do
to you, your daughter, and your wife?
No one knows specifically
if the CIA moved Ha-na out already,
or if she's still hidden somewhere
in South Korea.
I can find her if I become bait
and approach the CIA on my own.
I don't side with the North or America,
so it won't be an international conflict.
How can I trust you'll do it though,
an agent who got plastic surgery
to spy for seven years?
If you run, and abandon
your wife and your daughter,
that will only mean exposure
of our entire operation.
Then, um…
BD-7 can erase everything that I know.
Use it and send me South.
Carter. [breathing shakily]
BD-7.
How do you know that information?
Just give us this one chance.
And I'll get Ha-na
to the North, you'll see.
In exchange, you let us go.
[breathing shakily]
[groans]
-[Carter] Yoon Hee!
-[Jung Hee gasps] No!
-Yoon Hee!
-[Jung Hee] No!
-Yoon Hee! Yoon Hee!
-[Jung Hee sobbing] Yoon Hee!
-Yoon Hee.
Comrade Carter.
-[breathing angrily]
-[Jung Hee sobbing]
You must successfully
see this thing through.
-Because now…
-[Jung Hee sobbing]
…Yoon Hee's been infected.
[Jung Hee sobbing] Yoon Hee. Yoon Hee.
[sobbing] No.
[continues sobbing]
Yoon Hee. [sobbing]
Oh, my baby.
[sobbing]
[somber music playing]
[Carter panting]
[Jung Hee] Have your memories come back?
Do you… Do you remember us?
I'm sorry.
I left you here.
You went to save our family.
And well…
And you really did.
[thuds]
[Carter panting]
-[Jung Hee] Carter!
-[yelps]
Listen. Take the children first and run!
[grunts]
Ha-na, quickly.
If you move northwest,
you'll see a train coming in.
-Just hurry.
-[motorbike approaching]
What about you though?
Just worry about the children now.
-Doctor. Hurry!
-Hold on, Ha-na!
-Ha-na, you have to hold on tight!
-[gun firing]
-[Jung Hee] Hide behind the car.
[grunts]
[action music playing]
[guns firing]
-[gun fires]
-[grunts]
[grunts]
[Carter] Ha-na, hang on tight!
[Ha-na grunts]
[dramatic music playing]
DANDONG EMERGENCY MEDICAL COMMAND CENTER
[Carter grunts]
-[Ha-na grunts]
-[man yelps]
[music continues]
[Carter] Ha-na. Stay right here.
[grunts]
[grunting]
-[gun fires]
-[groans]
[grunting]
-[gun fires]
-[grunts]
[brakes squealing]
[bullet ricocheting]
[guns firing]
[grunts]
-[grunting]
-[gun fires]
[grunts]
[guns firing]
[soldiers yelling]
[grunts, yells]
-[Ha-na screams]
-[gun firing]
[Ha-na grunting]
-[grunting]
-[groaning]
[grunts]
[grunting]
[both grunting]
[gun firing]
[Ha-na screams]
No! Get away from me!
[Ha-na screaming]
[whirring]
[gun firing]
Ha-na grunting]
-[gun fires]
-[Ha-na grunts]
[guns firing]
[grunts]
[dramatic music playing]
Prepare to fire.
[music intensifies]
[exploding]
[frantic music playing]
-[knife swishing]
-[soldier groans]
[screaming in pain]
[knife swishing]
[screaming]
[grunts]
-[stabbing]
-[grunts]
[bullets ricocheting]
[frantic music continues]
[music warps]
[music resumes]
[bullets ricocheting]
[gun firing]
[yelling]
Go lower. Go lower!
[Ha-na grunts]
[yelling]
[gunfire continues]
[grunts]
[Dr. Jung] Hang on, Ha-na! Ha-na!
[Jung Hee] Ha-na! Take my hand! [grunts]
-[Ha-na yelps]
-[Jung Hee grunts]
[Ha-na screams]
[grunting]
-[Jung Hee grunts]
-[Ha-na grunts]
[grunting]
[sighs]
[yells]
[grunting]
-[grunts]
-[knife swishes]
[groans]
-[grunts]
-[pilot screams in pain]
-[gun fires]
-[grunting]
You sneaky shit. [breathing heavily]
So,
you think those memories
you finally regained
are memories that are really yours?
[grunting]
[screaming]
[grunts]
[grunts, pants]
[panting]
[yelps]
[grunting]
[gun firing]
[dramatic music playing]
[grunting]
[Jung Hee yelps, pants]
[yelps]
[grunting]
[both grunting]
-[yelling]
-[grunting]
[groans]
[screams in pain]
[Jung Hee] Doctor, get on before me!
[grunts]
[both grunting]
[exploding]
[suspenseful music playing]
[hopeful music playing]
[Jung Hee panting]
-[gasps] Yoon Hee.
-[Carter] Yoon Hee.
[gasps]
[sighs]
Yoon Hee, are you all right?
Do you recognize me?
[Yoon Hee] M-Mom.
[Jung Hee] Yes, it's me.
[Yoon Hee] Where are we going now?
[explodes]
[dramatic music playing]
[mellow music playing]